retrojamz.com 2019-03-14

# Privacy Policy

Last updated on May 21, 2018

RetroJamz recognizes that your privacy is very important and we take it seriously. This Privacy Policy (“Privacy Policy”) describes our policies and procedures on the collection, use, disclosure, and sharing of your personal information or personal data when you use the RetroJamz website. This Privacy Policy applies to activities by RetroJamz.com and its affiliates and subsidiaries (collectively “RetroJamz,” “we” or “us”). Capitalized terms that are not defined in this Privacy Policy have the meaning given to them in our [Terms of Service](https://retrojamz.com/legality/).

**What information does RetroJamz collect?**

RetroJamz collects information from you when you subscribe to our newsletter, respond to a survey or fill out a form.

When registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address or phone number. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

**What does RetroJamz use your information for?**

We do not sell your personal data – such as your name and contact information – to third parties to use for their own marketing purposes. Any of the information RetroJamz collects from you may be used in one of the following ways:

– To personalize your experience

(your information helps RetroJamz to better respond to your individual needs)

– To improve RetroJamz

(RetroJamz continually strives to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)

– To improve customer service

(your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)

– To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature

– To send periodic emails

The email address you provide may be used to send you information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.

**How does RetroJamz protect your information?**

RetroJamz implements a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information.

RetroJamz offers the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Database to be only accessed by those authorized with special access rights to our systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.

**Does RetroJamz use cookies?**

Our Site may use cookies to enhance User experience. Users web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. Users may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.

**Does RetroJamz disclose any information to outside parties?**

RetroJamz does not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**Unsubscription**

If you choose to unsubscribe from our mailing service, then all of your information will be removed from our servers, and it may not be restored by us, even if you change your mind. If you choose to unsubscribe, then you will no longer receive any communications from us. However, you can resubscribe any time.

**Third party links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, RetroJamz may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

**European Union’s General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) Compliance**

Because RetroJamz values your privacy, we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the European Union’s General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR). RetroJamz therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

**Your California Privacy Rights**

California law permits users who are California residents to request and obtain from us once a year, free of charge, a list of the third parties to whom we have disclosed their personal information (if any) for their direct marketing purposes in the prior calendar year, as well as the types of personal information disclosed to those parties. If you are a California resident and would like to request this information, please submit your request in an email to [requests@retrojamz.com](mailto:requests@retrojamz.com).

**Online Privacy Policy Only**

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

**Terms and Conditions**

Please also visit our [Terms and Conditions](https://retrojamz.com/legality/) section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website.

**Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our web site privacy policy.

**Advertising**

Any advertisements served on RetroJamz may be controlled using cookies. These cookies allow advertisers to display ads based on your visits to this site and other sites that use advertising services. Learn how to opt out of these advertising cookie usage. As mentioned above, any tracking done by them through cookies and other mechanisms is subject to their own privacy policies.

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If RetroJamz decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below.

**Contacting Us**

If there are any questions regarding this Privacy Policy, you may contact RetroJamz at [info@retrojamz.com](mailto:info@retrojamz.com), or send mail to using the information below:

RetroJamz

Attn: Admin

Ikoyi,

Lagos, Nigeria.
